I said that I was gonna start this vlog
a lot earlier but I slept with stormy
last night she woke me up at 6:00
wouldn't stop crying it wasn't it wasn't
the time to grab my camera and start
filming stormy is back asleep I'm about
to take a shower brush my teeth I have a
long day today and I'll tell you guys
about it after we show okay so I just
took a shower wash my face I have a
really long day today so I'm doing a
bunch of meetings I have like a cosmetic
meeting a skin meeting I gotta meet with
my mom my business manager I want to
show you guys my office I can't wait for
that also it's Arielle's birthday
Arielle is my makeup artist slash friend
and I am surprising him with a birthday
dinner because he said he wasn't doing
anything for his birthday I love
birthdays my phone is going off see this
is when the day starts I'm getting text
messages Kim we have a family group shot
my mom and lovely John who you will meet
today
okay so stay tuned we got a busy day I'm
not really gonna film glam because it's
not that exciting very quick breakfast
and then get into it okay I'm in the
middle of glam but I'm gonna wake stormy
up because she's got to go to the farm
and they're good
right now she is sooner
did you have a good thing laugh
are you gonna meet me at the office
today yes hi you what your glasses I
feel like I could wear and make all
these little custom t-shirts for her
this little talentless t-shirt do we
think white biker shorts guys are black
I'm gonna do black sand she's going to
the farm I love you I'm gonna finish
getting ready to okay so now I'm gonna
go get dressed
turn the camera around because Brian my
fitting room right now I might wear one
of these three dresses tonight I want to
or something pink because my whole
office is like black and pink I love
this Alexander Wang pink jacket with the
pink matching pants I also love this
pink little workers jumpsuit chose the
jumpsuit because I don't even have time
to think about it I paired it with these
white Chanel sneakers and just a little
silver hoop earrings to match the
buttons and some rings and then I found
these glasses which are pretty cute
so that's a look at the day and then
yeah now I gotta choose a purse
I'm thinking maybe white I gotta love
this little box
or clear which I like to I think I'm
gonna go with white because it's easy
okay think I'm gonna
take this guy today
now we're gonna go
[Music]
I'm gonna head on I can't wait for you
guys to see the hoppy office we're
double filming so you're filming and I'm
coming I'm shooting a flood we're doing
something special together look at us
we're so bright today wait can we
wearing gray oh this is an exciting day
we are I really don't know what we're
exactly what we're doing today but we
have like love coming okay well yeah
right we have a collab coming could hold
me for half I have to do a photo shoot
later otherwise I wouldn't have fallen
out
you're on my blog my blog vlog its vlog
mommy it's really good what are you
eating Chinese chicken salad okay so
we're gonna go to a little private
meeting that you guys can't come in on
but we will see you after for the kind
of cosmetic meeting stormy and her
cousins at the farm I cannot take this I
got I love you all right look Judith hi
Marie thank you so much
this looks delicious but what we want to
do is get all of these like the color
for the components and the deco and all
of that done what about cream
can we see this color with gold Kendall
on it and black and black of Kendall I
think we should do this for our
anniversary on the November 30th all
Gold's worked off the option - oh I hear
a little baby it's - come here baby
thank you guys
oh you like this oh you like this
[Music]
your car
Wow
okay I love you I love you well Cassie
you soon it's hard to manage
mom life and work life sometimes so
that's why I made her a bedroom here so
she could be with me and still have fun
the first SPF product for Kylie's skin
you see Stormy's and all my meetings she
really is
I for sure I want to do a highly skin
Kylie skin summer truck serve and serve
soft serve me stop serve ice cream ice
coffee hey just like super cute summer
vibes and sell the products at the same
time around our legs here
okay back this is your toner
oh so human mini face wash so cute all
right so I'm taking a little break I
might have a little snack I had to cut
you guys off on the chi-lites good
meeting because I don't want to ruin any
surprises but I'm gonna have a meeting
with my business manager and then I'm
gonna do some touch-ups and get into my
Kylie cosmetics a little photo shoot and
go to the other side of the office hi
you guys what are we about to do photo
shoot shoot new lip kiss alright so I'm
almost done for the day I'm gonna wait
for her Andrew look through her Isha's
makeup YUM I can't wait all right so I
changed into this lovely sexy robe I'm
gonna do some touch-ups and then get
right in and do these shots really quick
I'm really fast with these and then
we're off back home to change and
surprise Arielle tonight so yeah
Angelina is just gonna tell him Arielle
we got to go out we got to do something
for your birthday and she is gonna take
him to dinner and then we're all gonna
be there and surprise him all right we
just finished glamming with faroush and
i'm gonna do the first shot super quick
I'm wearing Hosey velvet right now
that's gonna be launching prepared
cosmetics Posie is one of my most
popular shades so I made it Belle
because I know people love my velvet
formula a lot why are you just blue can
be also am shooting bear mat bear is a
gorgeous
we're just nude this is what it looks
like what those will be launching on
Kylie cosmetics stay tuned on the
Instagram for that date let's go shoot
[Music]
okay so we just finished a full day at
the office we had meetings we did a
shoot and now off to our iou's birthday
dinner I'm literally gonna wear this
home Oh cuz I'm way too comfortable
[Music]
oh oh oh thank you so much just so used
to you just handling it
is awkward
since we have to drive to the city I'm
not gonna wear my dress I'm gonna change
when I meet Heather cuz I got to go pick
her up I'm hungry
I'm ready to eat and we're rushing down
there cuz we're late for an important
date all right we're coming for you baby
I have my dress right here because I
didn't minutes so but I just want to
talk to you guys about Kylie skin
restocking on June 5th I'm restocking
full sets the factory sets on June 1st
you can get everything on June 5th or if
you want to wait till June 10th that's
when I'll be restocking individual
products and I want to edit to a plug
lipcott never the name is
I'd look good in action so I put the
liner on and then I put the matte lip in
the center it's just
I hate you guys Arielle just nine he
boasted I hate surprises I hate when
people surprise me I'm not the type I
don't like the attention so I literally
cannot wait to surprise him
Wow now I wanna now I want to surprise
them even more Arielle I'm so sorry I
have to do this for you because I love
you okay
mission you think alright my huh how
they're just gone here we're getting in
the dress this dress
everything baby
all right here
okay I'm just leaving I was gonna say
bye I'm just gonna go to dinner I don't
even know maybe like midnight guy they
just cussed everybody out it's like your
sponsor ruined my surprise can't be on
time seriously no because I know where
Arielle is I'm on tops on RL but I told
everyone to be there at 8:00 and one
person is there but that's what I have
to do is surprise parties you got to
tell them 7:00 if you want them there at
9:00 like yeah it's bad I know
[Music]
made Angelina
stall hopefully he doesn't show up with
only I can't wait to make it he's almost
here he's about to pull up
[Music]
[Applause]
we've been having the best time
Mario's let's finish speed from the
bottom of my heart
[Music]
I adore you with all my heart and I
literally do any
[Music]
[Applause]
love you the night is over we're all
leaving
[Applause]
[Music]
I love you thank you for watching my
youtube channel subscribe like this
video make sure you comment down below
what you would like to see next from me
and give it a big thumbs out
[Music]